One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Inherited will...
the tides of time,
and humanity's dreams...
They cannot be stopped.
As long as people seek freedom,
these things will never cease to be.
It Begins
Crocodile!
Get out here!
I came all this way to kick your ass!
Crocod–
That's gonna have
the opposite effect!
He's considered the country's hero!
You wanna upset the patrons too?!
O-Okay! What do we do, then?!
J-Just slow down and wait for Vivi!
We need her to point out Crocodile!
Speaking of Vivi, where is she?
Vivi! Crocodile! Where are you?!
Hey!
Assistant Manager! A bunch
of weirdos just came inside!
Have security take care of 'em.
Don't cause a scene!
Hey! Vivi and Crocodile
aren't coming!
I've got you now, Straw Hat!
Smoker!
Just scurryin' around everywhere!
It's Smokey!
R-Run!
Damn! What's that smoke
freak doing here in Rainbase?!
Maybe he's got a thing for Luffy!
This building's surrounded by water!
Dead end!
Please stop, sir!
Government officials
aren't allowed inside!
Move!
He's so stubborn!
Get back here!
I can't deal with that guy!
Just a minute, sir.
I must ask that you leave–
Wh-What the...?!
Huh? Did I just run into something?
Manager! This is terrible!
A strange group of people have...
Send them to the VIP room.
Orders from the owner
Crocodile himself.
Stop!
Hey! Look there!
Thank you...
for coming!
Right this way!
This is the VIP room!
VIP room?!
He may as well be saying,
"Bring it on," right?!
This guy gets right to the point!
All right! Let's go!
VIP?! Does their connection
to Crocodile run that deep?!
Depending on what this uncovers,
I could send 'em all to the gallows!
But what's a VIP?!
Hey! The path splits!
VIPs... go to the left!
And it says pirates go this way!
Which way do we go?!
Hurry and decide!
VIPs, obviously! VIPs!
But we're pirates!
Pirates go this way!
V.I.P Pirate
Yeah! You got a point there!
W-Wait!
Straw Hat!
Huh?!
What the hell is this?!
I can't believe we fell for this trick.
It's my compelled-to-swim-when-
falling-in-darkness disease!
A trapdoor!
A clever trap.
Yeah. It got us good.
More like easily avoidable!
We played right into their hands!
You're the poster children for stupid!
Anyway... suddenly...
I feel so weak.
Why's that? You getting hungry?
Luffy!
I-I-I'll fight you
if you want, smoke freak!
I once helped take down
a bomb man!
Achoo...
Huh? I have no strength...
Just like when I fall in water.
What have you done to Luffy?!
At the tip of this jutte is
a material called seastone.
The going rumor is this strange stone
is found in just one sea.
Not much is known about it,
but it basically gives off
the same energy as the ocean.
You can think of it
as the sea in solid form.
So it makes Luffy weak?
Every jail cell at Navy Headquarters
is constructed with this stuff
to keep criminals with
devil fruit powers from escaping.
You're saying...
this prison cell is the same?
If it weren't,
I'd be long gone by now.
And you... I'd make it so you never take to sea again!
Wait! Wait! You're not actually
thinking of fighting in here, are you?!
Not to mention, he becomes smoke!
Swords are useless against him!
That's correct. Give it up.
You're going to die together...
so why not try and get along?
Crocodile!
What?!
So he's one of the Seven Warlords?
Looks as despicable as I thought.
Oho! You live up to your reputation
as a "wild dog," Smoker-kun.
It seems you never truly believed
I was on your side.
And indeed,
you would be correct.
Smoker. I think I'll have you die
an "accidental" death.
I'll inform the government
that you fought well
against the ragtag Straw Hat Pirates.
I don't know why you've come
to this country,
but I assume you're on your own.
The government would
never have sent you here
because we warlords
of the sea are trusted.
So you're that Crocodile guy?!
Hey! You! Fight me–
Pay attention! Don't touch the bars!
Straw Hat Luffy.
You've done well to come this far.
I promise to get rid of you,
all in due time.
Now we just need the guest of honor.
Guest of honor?
I just sent my partner to pick her up.
I can't afford to waste time
in a place like this!
You've put up quite
the fight, Princess.
I'd expect no less
from a former frontier agent!
But don't you think it's
time you accepted your fate?
I have to hurry to the others!
Now come! The boss is waiting!
Don't touch me!
Wh-What the...?! Is that a bird?!
A falcon?!
But why does a bird
have machine guns?!
It's huge!
Shoot it down!
Crap! The princess!
Pell! You came for me!
It is a joy to see you again,
Your Highness.
Please remain here a moment.
Pell?!
Not Pell the Falcon?!
H-He's Arabasta's mightiest warrior!
Bird-Bird Fruit: Falcon!
There are only five types
known to grant flight,
so savor this rare privilege!
S-Shoot! Shoot like crazy!
He vanished!
Flying Talons!
You are a lifesaver!
Now, I must hurry to the others!
Really? Aren't you
getting ahead of yourself?
You've been a real thorn in our side.
Miss All-Sunday!
It seems our precious employees
have been decommissioned.
Vice President...
Who are you?!
That was magnificent.
I've never seen someone who can fly.
But, are you stronger than me?
Princess Vivi, I take it these are
the ones threatening our homeland?
I'd like to invite the princess
to our mansion. What do you say?
How absurd!
This is out of the question!
Oh.
Don't screw with us!
Such language from a princess
is so unexpected, Miss Wednesday.
After what you did to Igaram...
Igaram? Oh, Mr. 8?
Don't tell me you killed Igaram-san ?!
What are you getting
so worked up for?
How was that any different
from what you did to our employees?
Don't be so petulant.
Damn you!
I will add you to Arabasta's
wealth of sand!
Tres Fleur.
Pell!
Your Highness! You are unhurt!
Did you think I had killed this girl?
D-Damn you! What did you do?!
Don't be so angry.
I'm just having a bit of fun with you.
You have devil fruit powers?!
That's right. I partook
of the Flower-Flower Fruit.
I can make any part of my body
bloom like flowers.
This is my ability.
My limbs can sprout from anywhere.
You can't escape my reach.
Escape?! Nonsense!
I will avenge Igaram-san
right here, right now!
So sorry. While I was indeed
enjoying this, playtime is over.
That's all right! This won't take long!
It seems you still don't understand.
Seis Fleur!
A submission hold?!
Power. Speed.
These mean nothing to me.
Clutch!
Pell!
He was the kingdom's
mightiest warrior?
N-No...
Now, off we go.
I'm not seeing this...
Our boss and your
friends are waiting.
Inside a prison cell
deep within Rain Dinners.
Look at me, I'm Sanji.
You the one who ate the meat?
Act like...
Collier!
Here's Zoro! "Oni!"
serious prisoners!
How can you act like that
when we're in a serious bind?!
We can't get out,
so what else is there to do?!
The fact we can't get out
is what makes it serious!
We might wind up dead
if we don't do something!
And why are you sleeping?!
Oh, is it morning?
It's noon!
You're a high-spirited girl.
Whatever! Go ahead
and act confident while you still can!
Once these guys get out of here,
they'll kick your butt and send you
flying above the clouds!
Isn't that right, Luffy?!
Of course it is, you jerk!
As a captain, you certainly instill
a lot of trust, Straw Hat Luffy.
Trust...
The most unneeded
thing in this world.
Where does he get off,
insulting us like that?!
Q-Quiet! You're gonna
upset him, too!
Crocodile!
Vivi!
Welcome, Vivi, princess of Arabasta!
No, Miss Wednesday!
I'm impressed you managed to evade
our assassins to come this far!
I would go as far as it takes...
to see you meet your demise, Mr. 0!
If only you hadn't come
to this country...
Wait! Vivi! Let us out!
Arabasta would've remained peaceful!
Peacock String Slasher!
It's no use.
Satisfied?
As a citizen of this country,
you must know
that I have the power
of the Sand-Sand Fruit.
Want to become a mummy?
A s-sand person!
Hey, you! Get away from Vivi!
I'll kick your ass!
Sit.
Perfect timing.
The party is just starting.
Isn't that right, Miss All-Sunday?
Right.
Party?
It just turned noon.
Operation Utopia is now underway.
Operation Utopia?
What's an "Operation Utopia"?
Hey!
It will be this pathetic little kingdom
that dies, Miss Wednesday.
I'm going to wipe Arabasta
from the face of the earth!
All people, big and small,
will be sucked into eternal darkness
as they writhe in pain.
Let Operation Utopia...
commence!
Video Editing
Gigglebot
Timing
PhosCity
Quality Control
Galaxy 9000 , JT-421, Pepperjack
Soundtracking
Halee
Graphics
Datenshi
Karaoke
KaitouYahiko
Subtitle Editing
Zenef
Translation
DemonRin , FUNimation
Raws
Neo-Raws